=== BREAKPOINT AI VERIFICATION ===
[+] OpenAI Key Detected: sk-test-...tion

[*] Testing Directory Summarization (Excluding common noise)...
[+] Summarized 46 relevant source files.

[*] Verifying AI Prompt Construction...
[+] SUCCESS: AI can see and summarize the codebase.
----------------------------------------
You are a senior security researcher. Given the following summary of a project's source code, determine which of these security attack modules are most applicable to test this project: ['sqli', 'xss', 'rce'].

Project Summary:
File: build_binary.py
Snippet: import PyInstaller.__main__
import shutil
import os

print("[*] Building Breakpoint Engine...")

# 1. Build Core Engine
# We use ; for Windows separator in add-data
PyIn...
----------------------------------------
